Guide to the Carl L. Withers Manuscript Collection RISM.MC.1
New York University Archives
- Series V. Photographs, 1947-1950
  - Subseries A. Mayajigua (Box 5)
    - Group 5
      - Tienda at Las [Llanades], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 2)
      - The Guagua - Road to Perea - stop at Las Llanades, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 3)
      - House (Perea) [advertisement] for dance - baptism, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 4)
      - MP [Manuel Picabea] at "La Violeta", 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 5)
      - Benito, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 6)
      - Farm and loading point: train to Nela [?], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 7)
      - The baracon: Nela, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 8)
      - Same, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 9)
      - Blind man, led by boy v. 16 and 17, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 10)
      - Corredor: looking toward Cabadonga, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 11)
      - Street in Mayajigua (downtown), 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 12)
      - Downtown street in Mayajigua, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 13)
      - La Violeta and Colonia Espanola, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 14)
      - Coredor: Saddles; boy carrying chair on head, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 15)
      - Old [man] of #10, sitting (v #10), 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 16)
      - Same as 16, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 17)
      - Jorge at mango tree, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 18)
      - Jorge, Roberto and Negro, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 19)
      - Mule train, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 20)
      - Pictures of La parranda, 1947, no negatives, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 21)
      - Pictures of La parranda, 1947, no negatives [missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-5 - 22)
    - Group 5 [BN]
      - Guajiro + baby (near baño) [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-5 - 1)
      - 4 negro cil [children] (near baño) under mango tree [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-5 - 2)
      - 3 negro boys (near baño) [with] toy 1 - wheeled cart - sledge, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-5 - 3)
      - Liceo - bright - time exposure [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-5 - 4)
      - boy w. girl w. big hat; (bottom dark), 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-5 - 5)
        [Missing]
      - Porch and table - house opp. Café carmen lourve, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-5 - 6)
      - The street - horses, women, car, 2 bread-baskets, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-5 - 7)
      - Many bootblacks, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-5 - 8)
    - Group 6
      - Negro (dancer - carpenter) upstairs Cobadunga [sp.], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 1)
      - Negro barker, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 2)
      - West End - house; clothes drying, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 3)
      - Boy w. toy, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 4)
      - Boy w. toy (rooster), 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 5)
      - 2 tiny boys, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 6)
      - Corner: houses, boy, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 7)
      - [Man] and Chinese boy, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 8)
      - [original comment crossed out, see M6 - 10 below, no photo], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 9)
      - Negro in [street], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 10)
      - The Negro Society, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 11)
      - A [street] in West End, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 12)
      - House [with] curtain blowing, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 13)
      - House [with] 2 pigeons in door, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 14)
      - A Riosko [sp.], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 15)
      - [Children] and baby, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-6 - 16)
    - Group 6 [BN]
      - Benito & Pepe-Porch of "La Reina", 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-6 - 1)
      - Carmen Liceo [Note: photograph stained], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-6 - 2)
      - Old man - entrance to Coradonga, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-6 - 3)
      - Delap'd [delapidated] wall - upstairs corredo, coradonga, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-6 - 4)
      - West end [?] St. - Guano houses; cil [children] (incl. Juarez), 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-6 - 5)
      - frame house - Cil [Children] in rear (incl. Chinito), 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-6 - 6)
      - frame houses; cil [children in] wheelbarrow [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-6 - 7)
      - people + cows, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-6 - 8)
    - Group 7
      - Carmita and puppy [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7- 1)
      - Women and children (who begged for picture), 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 2)
      - Vieja and CW [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 3)
      - All on log [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 4)
      - Carmita and CW [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 5)
      - Mulato (sic) and Chinito [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 6)
      - M.P.'s [Manuel Picabea] siblings, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 7)
      - M.P.'s [Manuel Picabea] siblings, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 8)
      - M.P.'s [Manuel Picabea] siblings, 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 9)
      - Mule train [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 10)
      - RR [station], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 11)
      - RR [station] [Carl Withers in center], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 12)
      - RR [station] [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 13)
      - RR [station] (the farmicidos) Withers' note: "My seeing off", 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 14)
      - RR [station], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 15)
      - RR [station], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 16)
      - Group of men and boys [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-7 - 21)
    - Group 7 [BN]
      Note: Withers descriptions begin with photo 5
      - Negro Society - Nueva Gerona, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-7 - 1)
      - Horace race - Nueva Gerona, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-7 - 2)
      - Horace race - Nueva Gerona, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-7 - 3)
      - Types of poor boys - Nueva Gerona, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-7 - 4)
      - Last of horse race - Nueva Gerona, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-7 - 5)
      - Cabanas + Rancho Chico, Baheano, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-7 - 6)
      - Cabanas + Rancho Chico, Baheano, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-7 - 7)
      - Bohio where old man died (near barn), 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-7 - 8)
    - Group 8 [BN]
      - [No comment or photo], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-8 - 1)
      - [No comment or photo], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-8 - 2)
      - [No comment or photo], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-8 - 3)
      - A negro fam (where?), 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-8 - 4)
      - bride and groom approaching church door [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-8 - 5)
        See oversized photos, Box 8
      - [bride] + [groom] entering sta. wagon [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-8 - 6)
      - crowd around sta. wagon, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-8 - 7)
      - 2 girls - day of the wedding [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-8 - 8)
    - Group 8 Mayajigua [No negatives]
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object M-8 - 1, 3, 4, 5)
      - [Two young children, one with walking stick], undated (Box 5, Object M-8 - 2)
      - [Woman stands in doorway], undated (Box 5, Object M-8 - 6)
    - Group 8
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object M-8 - 7)
      - [Horse grazes outside house], undated (Box 5, Object M-8 - 8)
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object M-8 - 9 thru M-8 - 13)
      - [Distant view of house and palm trees], undated (Box 5, Object M-8 - 14)
      - [Small group sitting on porch], undated (Box 5, Object M-8 - 15)
      - [View of train carrying produce?], undated (Box 5, Object M-8 - 16)
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object M-8 - 17 thru M-8 - 18....)
      - [Animals in a corral], undated (Box 5, Object M-8 - 19)
    - Group 9 [BN]
      - Jorge Juarez, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN- 9 - 1)
      - Osmel, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN- 9 - 2)
      - Osmel, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN- 9 - 3)
      - Eberto [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN- 9 - 4)
      - Manolo Banza - Sweetheart - Excursion al Bahmeanio, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN- 9 - 5)
      - [No comments/no photo], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-9 - 6)
      - Black [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-9 - 7)
      - [No comments/no photo], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-9 - 8)
    - Group 9 Marita's School
      - [Distant view of the school], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-9 - 1)
      - [Group of children with teacher outside school], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-9 - 2)
      - [Children line up outside school], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-9 - 3)
      - [Children entering school], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-9 - 4)
      - [Children outside school], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-9 - 5)
      - [Closer view of children outside school], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-9 - 6)
      - [Closer view of children outside school], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-9 - 7)
      - [Inside view of classroom], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-9 - 8)
    - Group 10 [BN] [No negatives]
      - Lucia (maid at R's house), 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-10 - 1)
      - Roberto's hermanita, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-10 - 2)
      - Roberto's b. Elisito + latter's friend, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-10 - 3)
      - Teo - upstairs [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-10 - 4)
      - Teo - upstairs, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-10 - 5)
      - Tacolo in kitchen, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-10 - 6)
      - Ramon, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-10 - 7)
      - Gonzales Canetti + new toy, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-10 - 8)
    - Group 10: A trip with Marcelo to the Isleños
      - [Woman poses with three children], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 1)
      - [Distant view of same individuals], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 2)
      - [Plough animal; boy stands nr. log], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 3)
      - [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 4)
      - [Young boy feeding a bird], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 5)
      - [Distant view of farmer with plough animals], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 6)
      - [Closer view same image], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 7)
      - [Same image, different angle], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 8)
      - [Distant view of house, palm trees]], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 9)
      - [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 10)
      - [Distant view of house and fields], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 11)
      - [Distant view of farm and fields], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 12)
      - [Distant view of house at the foot of mountain], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 13)
      - [Family poses outside of house], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 14)
      - [View of mountain], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 15)
      - [Closer view of thatch covered house, outdoor cooking vessels; boy at right], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 16)
      - [Woman holds two food items], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 17)
      - [Small tree in foreground; house in distance], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 18)
      - [Boy walks down wooded path], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 19)
      - [Distant view of house], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 20)
      - [Distant view of house], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 21)
      - [Distant view of individuals next to house], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 22)
      - [View of crops and stream], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 23)
      - [Boy and a pig], 1948 (Box 5, Object M-10 - 24)
    - Group 11 [[BN] [No negatives]
      - Ro's [Robert's] hermanito, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-11 - 1)
      - double exposure of same, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-11 - 2)
      - Man who wanted picture taken, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-11 - 3)
      - R's m [Robert's mother], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-11 - 4)
      - Boy on pot (friends of Doña Maria), 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-11 - 5)
      - Baby in bed, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-11 - 6)
      - Baby in bed; boy sucking thumb, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-11 - 7)
      - Alfredo Socorras, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-11 - 8)
    - Group 11 - Tamarindo, Chambas, inside railroad car, circus
      - [Street with individuals on bikes and horses], undated (Box 5, Object M-11 - 1)
      - [Houses in background; sign reads "Tamarindo"], undated (Box 5, Object M-11 - 2)
      - [Rural landscape], undated (Box 5, Object M-11 - 3)
      - [House with large log in front, "Chambas" written on back], undated (Box 5, Object M-11 - 4)
      - [Four boys pose for camera], undated (Box 5, Object M-11 - 4[A])
      - [Inside railroad car], undated (Box 5, Object M-11 - 5)
      - [Church on left; circus tent to the right], undated (Box 5, Object M-11 - 5[A])
      - [Woman with small boy; pose near sign that reads "Los Negros"], undated (Box 5, Object M-11 - 6)
      - [Road leading toward houses, palm trees], undated (Box 5, Object M-11 - 7)
      - [Same scene out of focus], undated (Box 5, Object M-11 - 8)
      - [A stand of trees], undated (Box 5, Object M-11 - 9)
      - [Rural scene out of focus/overexposed], undated (Box 5, Object M-11 - l0)
    - Group 12 [BN] [No Negatives]
      - [No comment or photograph], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-12 - 1)
      - Dona Maria, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-12 - 2)
      - Dona Maria, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-12 - 3)
      - Dona Maria, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-12 - 4)
      - Teo, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-12 - 5)
      - Eberto, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-12 - 6)
      - Pedro [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-12 - 7)
      - Roberto's [mother] + hermanito, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-12 - 8)
    - Group 12 -- after Trinidad? A walk thru potrero, tienda on highway...
      - [Old rotting tree?], undated (Box 5, Object M-12 - 1)
      - [Thatched house among trees], undated (Box 5, Object M-12-2)
      - [Children pose for the camera; thatched roof house in background], undated (Box 5, Object M-12 - 3)
      - [Similar view], undated (Box 5, Object M-12 - 4)
      - [Close up of thatched roof house], undated (Box 5, Object M-12 - 5)
      - [Another view of same house], undated (Box 5, Object M-12 - 6)
      - [Distant view of same type houses], undated (Box 5, Object M-12 - 7)
      - [Small thatched house], undated (Box 5, Object M-12 - 8)
      - [Wider view of landscape, house on the right], undated (Box 5, Object M-12 - 9)
      - [Intersecting roads], undated (Box 5, Object M-12 - 10)
      - [Rural landscape], undated (Box 5, Object M-12 - 11)
      - [Children at play], undated (Box 5, Object M-12 - 12)
      - [Individuals stand in front of thatched roof house], undated (Box 5, Object M-12 - 13)
      - [Crops with palm trees in background], undated (Box 5, Object M-12 - 14)
      - [Three men walk along a highway], undated (Box 5, Object M-12 - 15)
      - [Group of men stand on highway], undated (Box 5, Object M-12 - 16)
    - Group 13 -- Walk to tomato cannery with Manolo B., his C., bootblack, stealing cane, train
      - [Partial view of Mayajigua train station; horses on the street], undated (Box 5, Object M-13 - 1)
      - [Young boy sits in front of shoeshine stand], undated (Box 5, Object M-13 - 2)
      - [Two boys pose for camera], undated (Box 5, Object M-13 - 3)
      - [Railroad train], undated (Box 5, Object M-13 - 4)
      - [Man and boy pose by railroad car], undated (Box 5, Object M-13 - 5)
      - [Tomato cannery?], undated (Box 5, Object M-13 - 6)
      - [Workers line up steel pipes], undated (Box 5, Object M-13 - 7)
      - [Man leads cow from water], undated (Box 5, Object M-13 - 8)
      - [Same as above, different view], undated (Box 5, Object M-13 - 9)
      - [Young man poses by large tree], undated (Box 5, Object M-13 - 10)
      - [Distant view of thatched house], undated (Box 5, Object M-13 - 11)
      - [Machinery and truck], undated (Box 5, Object M-13 - 12)
      - [Machinery and truck], undated (Box 5, Object M-13 - 13)
      - [Young man poses by tree trunk], undated (Box 5, Object M-13 - 14)
      - [Train carrying sugar cane], undated (Box 5, Object M-13 - 15)
    - Group 13 [BN] [No negatives] (Box 5)
      - [Woman holds up baby], 1948 [?] (Box 5, Object BN-13 - 1)
        See Group 12 [BN], photo 2, 3
      - [Four children pose in the doorway of a store], 1948 [?] (Box 5, Object BN-13 - 2)
      - [Young woman poses for the camera], 1948 [?] (Box 5, Object BN-13 - 3)
      - [Missing], 1948 [?] (Box 5, Object BN-13 - 4)
      - [Same woman as BN-13 - 3, with two young men], 1948 [?] (Box 5, Object BN-13 - 5)
      - [Young man in BN-13 - 5 poses for the camera], 1948 [?] (Box 5, Object BN-13 - 6)
      - [Missing], 1948 [?] (Box 5, Object BN-13 - 7)
      - [Missing], 1948 [?] (Box 5, Object BN-13 - 8)
    - Group 14 [No negatives] (Box 5)
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object M-14 - 1)
      - [Young boy putting on his shirt], undated (Box 5, Object M-14 - 2)
      - [All missing], undated (Box 5, Object M-14 - 3 thru M-14 - 10)
      - [A grove of palm trees], undated (Box 5, Object M-14 - 11)
    - Group 14 [BN] [No negatives] (Box 5)
      - Four children playing a game, undated (Box 5, Object BN-14 - 1)
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object BN-14 - 2)
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object BN-14 - 3)
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object BN-14 - 4)
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object BN-14 - 5)
      - [Top half of photo: a painting of a house, bottom half: advertisements and a clock], undated (Box 5, Object BN-14 - 6)
      - [Three young men pose for the camera], undated (Box 5, Object BN-14 - 7)
      - [Young man and his black cat pose for the camera], undated (Box 5, Object BN-14 - 8)
    - Group 15 (lat trip) [Nacy?] Camaguey [?)] (Box 5)
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object M-15 - 1)
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object M-15 - 2)
      - [Urban scene; sign reads "Casa Koricki"], undated (Box 5, Object M-15 - 3)
      - [Woman in plaid shirt poses for camera], undated (Box 5, Object M-15 - 4)
      - [Freight plane and cargo], undated (Box 5, Object M-15 - 5)
      - [Woman in plaid shirt poses in tree], undated (Box 5, Object M-15 - 6)
      - [Palm trees - "8 Palms" written on back of photo], undated (Box 5, Object M-15 - 7)
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object M-15 - 8)
      - [Another view of palm trees], undated (Box 5, Object M-15 - 9)
      - [Distant view of palm trees; fence on the left], undated (Box 5, Object M-15 - 10)
      - [Distant view of palm trees; same fence on the right], undated (Box 5, Object M-15 - 11)
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object M-15 - 12)
      - [Young man poses for the camera], undated (Box 5, Object M-15 - 13)
    - Group 15 [BN] [No Negatives] (Box 5)
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object BN-15 - 1)
      - [Boy standing in alley], undated (Box 5, Object BN-15 - 2)
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object BN-15 - 3)
      - [Distant view of a family standing in front of their home], undated (Box 5, Object BN-15 - 4)
      - [Young boy wearing a cap holds fish], undated (Box 5, Object BN-15 - 5)
      - [Man riding a horse on the street], undated (Box 5, Object BN-15 - 7)
      - [Two boys carrying large palm frond], undated (Box 5, Object BN-15 - 8)
    - Group 16 [120 Box camera] (Box 5)
      - [Five children pose for the camera], 1949 [?] (Box 5, Object M-16 - 1)
      - [Young boy gestures toward birds], 1949 [?] (Box 5, Object M-16 - 2)
      - [Group of children gather around mother and baby], 1949 [?] (Box 5, Object M-16 - 3)
      - [Three children pose for the camera], 1949 [?] (Box 5, Object M-16 - 4)
      - [Man holds farm animals by rope; onlookers in the background], 1949 [?] (Box 5, Object M-16 - 5)
      - [Children playing a game; palm in back], 1949 [?] (Box 5, Object M-16 - 6)
        See also mounted photos
      - [Same individuals in M-16 - 5], 1949 [?] (Box 5, Object M-16 - 7)
      - [Young woman poses outside building], 1949 [?] (Box 5, Object M-16 - 8)
    - Group 16 [BN] [No negatives] (Box 5)
      - [Women and young girls stand in front of church], undated (Box 5, Object BN-16 - 1)
      - [Missing], undated (Box 5, Object BN-16 - 2 thru BN-16 - 8)
    - Group 17 [BN] (Box 5)
      - Tiny boy carrying great palm frond to bakery [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-17 - 1)
      - 3 negritos posing in st. [street] [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-17 - 2)
      - Pepe (good!) [Missing], 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-17 - 3)
      - Backyard near tostadero, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-17 - 4)
      - Café - louvre carmen (dominoes inside), 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-17 - 5)
      - Youths + lizard, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-17 - 6)
      - Procession, lizard hunt, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-17 - 7)
      - Tulito, Rob, Jorge, Jose Luis, Las Casas, Pedro - dominoes, 1948 (Box 5, Object BN-17 - 8)
    - Group 18 [BN] [No negatives]
      - [Woman leads a dog on a leash], undated (Box 5, Object BN-18 - 4)
      - [Two young men pose for the camera], undated (Box 5, Object BN-18 - 6)
    - Group 19 [BN] [No negatives]
      - [Elderly woman poses for the camera], undated (Box 5, Object BN-19 - 2)
      - [Three young boys pose for the camera], undated (Box 5, Object BN-19 - 3)
      - [Horses are led by a man on horseback], undated (Box 5, Object BN-19 - 7)
    - Group 20 [BN] [No negatives]
      - [Woman holds young girl], undated (Box 5, Object BN-20 - 1)
      - [Small boy poses for the camera], undated (Box 5, Object BN-20 - 3)
    - Group 21 [BN] [No negatives]
      - [Young boy stands behind a fence], undated (Box 5, Object BN-21 - 6)
      - [Family stands outside of thatched roof home], undated (Box 5, Object BN-21 - 7)
    - Group 22 [BN] [No negatives]
      - [Group poses for the camera], undated (Box 5, Object BN-22 - 1)
      - [Young boy and two girls pose for the camera], undated (Box 5, Object BN-22 - 2)
    - Mounted Photos
      General
      These items are missing from this collection.
  - Subseries B. Trinidad (Box 6)
    - Group 1
      - Bull cart (rear), 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 1)
      - [Children] in street, 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 2)
      - [Children] and barrow, 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 3)
      - Lumber yard: logs, 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 4)
      - Corner: Cabildo of St. Caterina, 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 5)
      - [Comment crossed out], 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 6)
      - [House?] of Santera, 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 7)
      - AST, 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 8)
      - Pan Am office, 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 9)
      - The arbor in square, 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 10)
      - The church near sq, 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 11)
      - Boy selling brooms, 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 12)
      - Breaking rocks to pave [street], 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 13)
      - Cows and house at edge of airport, 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 14)
      - The plane is landing, 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 15)
      - Passengers go aboard, 1948 (Box 6, Object T-1 - 16)
    - Group 2 [contains slide]
      - [Distant view of a town], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 1)
      - [Houses on a cobblestone street], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 2)
      - [Close view of town buildings], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 3)
      - [Four young boys], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 4)
      - [Distant view of boys on a cobblestone street], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 5)
      - [Young boy gazing left], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 6)
      - [Church with bell tower], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 7)
      - [People walking in plaza], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 8)
      - [Historic plaque on building], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 9)
      - [Man on horse; building with sign "La Campesena" in the background], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 10)
      - [Woman and child in doorway], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 11)
      - [Children gather around a car], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 12)
      - [Distant view of house; mountains in background], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 13)
      - [Woman in doorway watching a dog], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 14)
      - [Group stands on cobbled street], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 15)
      - [Goat trotting along the street], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 16)
      - [Children and goat near houses], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 17)
      - [Man carries a ladder], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 18)
      - [Elaborate iron work doorway], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 19)
      - View of houses amid foliage, undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 20)
    - Group 2
      - [Young boy poses for camera], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 21)
      - [Group of young children pose for the camera], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 22)
      - [Children stand and sit in doorway], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 23)
      - [Another group poses in doorway], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 24)
      - [Man on horse talks with woman in doorway], undated (Box 6, Object T-2 - 25)